Did you think I couldn't find you if you hid?
My work is stressful enough.
And you still make trouble for me every day.
Always yelling about a divorce.
Are you seeing someone else?
No, I'm not.
No, no.
Don't let me catch you.
How dare you resist!
Let me ask you one thing.
Still want a divorce?
No.
Divorce?
Don't even think about getting rid of me.
You follow wherever I go.
Who is it?
Sir, your package.
Just leave it at the front desk.
This requires your signature in person.
Honey.
I won't hit you anymore.
But if you run away again,
I will kill you.
Why do you still smell so good?
Wait for me a moment.
That's what happened.
She was afraid of being controlled by Li Ting again.
So before Li Ting woke up,
she had to strike first.
I see.
That explains
why there were signs of a second impact on his head.
Exactly.
But...
What does this have to do with Dong Shan?
Why would he help Lu Chen?
Captain Zhuang.
I found something.
Look.
I found this
in Dong Shan's factory.
He secretly took all the photos in here.
This might be
the reason he helped Lu Chen.
You secretly took so many photos of Lu Chen.
Did she know?
What was your purpose in doing this?
Is this behavior any different from Li Ting's?
No different at all.
Very perverted.
I am not like him.
How so?
I am sincere towards Xiao Lu.
You don't know,
nor did you see
how Xiao Lu was tortured by Li Ting.
A life worse than death,
covered in bruises.
For a scumbag like him,
dying a hundred times wouldn't be enough.
Brother Shao.
Oh.
Downstairs at Lu Chen's place,
we found that cleaner's uniform.
And the clothes she wore during the crime,
which still had Li Ting's blood on them.
Dong Shan, the evidence is conclusive now.
Don't hide it anymore.
I can see you really wanted Li Ting dead.
I can also see you love her very much.
That day you deliberately led us to the dark room
to speak out for Lu Chen,
didn't you?
Today is your best chance.
Lu Chen definitely cannot escape the charges.
But if you can tell the whole truth,
maybe I can fight for a lighter sentence for her.
Can I trust you?
You can only trust me.
Okay.
I'll tell you.
I'll tell you everything.
I'm a private detective.
Six months ago,
Li Ting hired me
to find his missing wife, Lu Chen.
All expenses were covered.
It was a lucrative job.
Boss Li.
Mr. Dong.
Well,
it's like this.
My wife and I just had an argument.
She even turned off her phone.
I really can't get in touch with her.
With this kind of thing,
I can't exactly contact her friends.
I don't want to wash our dirty linen in public.
I understand.
So please, I really need your help to find her.
Here's the thing.
We don't usually take this kind of job.
My wife,
is very naive.
I'm really worried something might happen to her.
I just want to find her now.
This job might be small,
but...
The fee won't be small.
This is the deposit.
Here is the information.
Wait for my good news.
I searched for a long time.
I finally found her.
She is so beautiful,
like sunshine.
I suddenly had a selfish urge
to possess her.
But ultimately,
I chose to rationally
complete this mission.
Boss.
We found the person.
But I never expected
that my action
would bring a terrible disaster upon her.
Let me go!
Still trying to run?
Let go.
Help me.
Come here!
Let go!
Help!
You run.
Like running, huh?
Run again and I'll kill you.
Mr. Li.
Ignore her.
Help me.
Here.
Count it.
Mr. Li.
When you first came to me,
didn't you say
it was just a couple's quarrel?
Please.
What do you mean?
She's my wife.
I can do whatever I want.
Just do your job.
Don't meddle in my family affairs.
Let me go.
Be quiet!
I know I did something wrong.
I want to make up for it.
But
he hid her away.
I was always worried about her.
So I went to the hotel where Li Ting stayed
and applied to be a security guard.
I wanted to find
some clues about her.
Hello.
Is this Xinmai Hotel?
Are you still hiring security guards?
I successfully got a job at the hotel.
But I rarely saw Li Ting,
let alone Lu.
Until
that day.